I want you to wear this bracelet.
You're going to tell your dad
that she isn't the real Claire.
You think he'll believe you?
Put this drug in Claire's drink.
Once she passes out, take her to a room.
I trusted you.
But you turned me into a tool.
The Kanchathara family
has enough money to buy anyone's life.
I'll just find another woman
- to replace you as Claire.
- I hate you!
They found GHB in the pilot's blood.
The pilot must have
been drugged before he boarded.
And the only one who can tell us
what happened is...
I hate you.
I hate you! Do you hear me? I hate you!
Please sign here.
Hello?
I'm not coming in today.
The chairman?
What is he doing at the office?
- Hello.
- Oh, hello. I trust you're all doing well.
- Yes, sir.
- Thanks a lot.
Claire must be glad
you came to support her.
- Good morning, sir.
- Oh, morning.
Alright, I'll be right there.
The chairman's there?
Do you think this is about
Ms. Cha's suspicion about Ms. Jin?
I don't know what they're up to.
Listen, you go to the office.
I'll pick her up and follow you.
Okay.
Dad, what brings you to the office today?
Nothing much.
He wanted to surprise Claire.
He thought since she just started working,
she might still be adjusting.
So he came to support her.
And besides surprising Claire,
I also came because you asked me to, Rin.
I'm glad you asked me
to come and support Claire.
Thank you.
Well, we're family after all.
So, are Chan and Claire busy?
Why aren't they here to welcome him?
Hey, it's fine. Let them do their work.
I just came to surprise
and congratulate her.
Let's not disrupt their work.
Well...
Well what? What's wrong?
Dad, Chan and Claire didn't come in today.
At first, I thought you came
because you knew about the problem.
What problem?
Here's your tea.
Switching the project
we're launching on the 60th anniversary?
That's right, Dad.
I've already discussed it with the board.
Everyone agrees.
So I'm choosing The Paradise project,
that Chris and I manage, to replace it.
Here it is, sir.
What's the reason?
Not because you want the credit, is it?
I understand why you'd think that.
But if we don't choose a backup project,
I think TGL's 60th anniversary
will be postponed indefinitely.
Why's that?
I asked what the problem is.
Well, we won't have
the drawings to present to the clients.
We're having trouble opening the vault
where the Agriv project drawings are kept.
What's the problem? Why can't you open it?
The facial scanner outside the vault
suddenly didn't recognize
Claire's face, Dad.
I don't know why either.
That's why we must choose
a backup project for the event.
Does Chan know about this?
Yes.
Then get Chan to see me.
Dad, shouldn't we just choose
another project right now?
Right now.
Yes, Dad.
Get over here.
Cha.
- Why did you make me bring your dad here?
- Duh.
To show him that the vault won't open.
Cha.
Tell me you don't think Claire failing
the facial scan proves she's an imposter.
Proves what?
What's going on here?
Claire failed
the facial scan for the vault.
So Cha thinks she isn't the real Claire.
Are you crazy?
Just because she failed the facial scan?
The scanner might just be glitching.
Don't tell me you made me
bring your dad here just for this.
Yes. Because she failed the scan.
So what?
If she keeps failing,
what do you think Dad will think?
He'll think the scanner is glitching.
He won't get this crazy idea.
Mom, if she really fails the scan,
Dad will make her do it again.
And after 100 or 1,000 times,
she'll still fail.
Do you get it now, Mom?
Hey.
You need to come to
the office with me now.
Hey.
Claire left in a delivery truck?
How could you let her?
What if something happens to her?
We tried to stop her.
She said she'd fire us
if we didn't let her.
She also ordered us not to tell you.
Should I call the driver to see
where he dropped her off?
No need. Get back to work.
I'm sorry.
Tun, what's up?
Chan, Ms. Cha told the chairman
we can't open the vault
to replace Claire's project with hers.
If you don't want him to switch it,
bring Claire here now.
Ms. Cha.
Let me talk to Chan.
You heard that, right?
That my dad is going to replace
Claire's project with mine.
Ms. Cha, you just won't stop, will you?
Come on now, Chan.
No need to be that angry.
I did nothing wrong this time.
It's you and Claire
who can't open the vault.
Look, if you don't want my dad
to switch the project,
just bring Claire here now.
And it looks like my dad wants
an explanation from you.
Hurry up.
Chan, I think we should bring her here.
The chairman is angry like she said.
I'd love to do that too.
But... But Claire is missing.
What?
Look, I'll check the hospital
to see if she went to see her aunt.
No need.
I need you to do something first.
What?
If the chairman found out
what you did to Ms. Claire last night,
he wouldn't be pleased.
And he'd know what you're trying to do.
Is that a threat?
Let's call it
a mutual exchange of benefits.
No wonder you're just a bodyguard.
You don't even understand
something so simple.
An exchange of benefits
requires both things to have equal value.
But what you're using to bargain
doesn't even compare.
- Ms. Cha.
- Stop this nonsense.
And bring Claire here.
If that's all, get out.
Or people will think you switched sides.
I will tell everyone I'm not Ms. Claire.
My name is Jinla.
The woman whose life you turned into hell.
And do you think I'd let you do that?
I'll just find another woman
to replace you as Claire.
You're well aware.
The Kanchathara family
has enough money to buy anyone's life.
I'll just have to find...
another woman to replace you as Claire.
Did you want to see me?
Cha told me about the vault.
I wanted an explanation from you.
Where's Claire?
Oh, right. Where is Claire?
Ms. Claire told me she felt dizzy.
So I let her rest at home.
What?
Then what about the vault?
What are you going to do?
Is it because
the scanner is glitching or what?
I think there's a problem
with the scanner, sir.
But I've contacted the overseas team
to send someone over.
Really?
But I had the installation engineer
and the technical team check it.
They said the scanner works fine.
How about this?
If it's really an error like you said,
have Claire try again.
Could you give me another week?
We've waited this long.
I'd rather wait for the overseas engineer
to take a look in person to be sure.
A week?
Are you crazy?
You know we don't have time.
Chan.
If there's a problem,
you should just tell me.
Hello.
Okay.
Dad. No need to wait.
Because Claire just got here.
Ms. Claire.
Good morning.
You're feeling better now, right?
Why are you asking me that?
Well...
Oh, Claire!
Grandpa?
You're here.
I was free, so I stopped by.
I wanted to see you work too.
And now Dad knows that you failed
the facial scan to get into the vault.
What did Chan say about it?
Can't you think for yourself?
Why do you ask Chan about everything?
You don't need his input here,
because entering the vault
only requires your face.
Dad, should we have
Claire try to open the vault now?
- Sir, I think...
- Let's go, Claire.
Come on.
Good morning, sir.
Why are you up here?
Don't you know only senior executives
are allowed here?
The engineer in charge is sick today.
So I came up to stand by
in case the scanner glitches again.
How is that your job?
Tun is in charge of security here.
So the vault is also
his direct responsibility.
How long are
you going to talk over my head?
Can we open the door now?
Yes, sir.
Claire.
Stand here and look at the camera.
Try again.
Well?
Didn't you say the scanner worked fine?
It does.
Don't worry.
The scanner might be glitching. Try again.
Dad, I think we should stop here.
Because if it locks us out,
we'll have a big problem.
Maybe wait until after
the 60th anniversary to get it fixed.
Ms. Cha, did you forget the system allows
three attempts before it locks us out?
I didn't forget.
You're the one who forgot.
But if you want to try, go on ahead.
Because if it locks us out,
we'll just switch to another project.
- Go ahead.
- Chan.
Well?
Try again.
Got any more doubts, Ms. Cha?
Hold on.
Only Ms. Claire and the chairman
are allowed in the vault.
It was you.
What did you do to the scanner?
That's enough!
When will you stop being a problem?
Go! Get lost.
You too, Rin.
I'll take Claire inside.
I want to spend some time with her.
Claire, let's go.
Let's go, Mom.
Hey, do you have any idea
how nerve-racking that was?
If she failed the scan, both you and I,
and Ms. Jinla, would be done for.
We're lucky today that
we could edit Claire's iris data.
Thanks a lot, Tun.
Luckily, I kept Claire's body
for a situation like this.
Done.
But the hard part is
we must swap Claire's iris data
with Jinla's in time.
I need you to do something first.
Once we unlock
the vault with Claire's iris,
you must quickly replace it with Jinla's.
- Do it now.
- Yes, sir.
Is it done?
50%.
Hurry the hell up.
Good morning, chairman.
Another 20%.
Well? Didn't you say
the scanner worked fine?
It does.
Try again.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two...
Done.
I'd appreciate it if, instead of thanks,
you stopped giving me heart attacks.
Anyway, what do you think...
the chairman went into the vault for?
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
I just feel like...
he went in to look for something.
What do you think?
How is it?
Does being in this room
remind you of anything?
No.
Do you know what I call this room?
I call it "the room of memories."
Look at this project.
My first project.
It made me who I am today.
Recall anything about Rossarin?
It's fine.
I knew this might not work.
Stay in here for a while.
Maybe you might remember something.
Okay.
Hey.
Stop lashing out.
Isn't this embarrassing enough for you?
If I'd know you made me bring
Mr. Thiwa for this nonsense,
I wouldn't have agreed.
How?
How did she pass the scan? How?!
Good morning, chairman.
Yes.
Tunlathon.
Tunlathon was already there.
He must've done something to the scanner.
He was already there.
Hey, Cha.
Cha! Come back and talk to me, Cha!
The chairman is leaving soon.
Clear the area in front of the building.
Increase security.
Tell all related personnel that
if any visitors arrive with their cars,
have them park in the back.
And make sure all of you
are extra careful with weapon checks.
- Yes, sir.
Get out.
Get out!
It was you, wasn't it?
Why did the scanner work?
That.
If you're thinking...
I had an engineer fix the scanner,
you're right, Ms. Cha.
Wait, but to be precise, I should say
I just had them clean it a bit.
Last time, Ms. Claire failed the scan
because something was on the lens.
It caused the angle of the laser
to be slightly off.
Do you think I'm one of your buddies?
You're nothing more than Claire's dog.
Are you sure
that I'm nothing more than a dog?
What do you mean?
You're well aware
that I'm more than that.
Should I remind you...
what I used to be to you?
I should go check on the chairman.
Are you coming home with me?
It seems Claire
prefers to leave with Chan.
Is that so? Then hurry
and take care of everything, Chan.
And if there's any problem
you can't decide on, come to me.
Yes, sir.
Hurry back when you're done.
I will, Grandpa.
Why did he want you in the vault?
He knew I wasn't Ms. Claire.
So I had to tell him the truth
about who I am.
Hey.
Aren't you shocked at all?
I just said I told the chairman the truth.
You think if you told him the truth,
he would just get in the car and leave?
Huh?
Next time you make a joke,
think before you speak.
I wanted to shock you for a change.
Why did you leave me with him?
Weren't you worried I'd get caught?
So why did he want you in the vault?
He just thought if I went in there,
my memory might return.
I shouldn't have helped you.
You knew I'd visit my aunt, didn't you?
I was so mad at you.
You made me feel worthless.
Like I didn't exist.
So I wanted to see my aunt one last time
before I leave this world.
Ms. Nalin's condition is improving.
My aunt is getting better?
- Did she wake up?
- No.
But last night, Ms. Nalin could breathe
on her own without the ventilator
for about 10 minutes.
And why did she suddenly get better?
Medically,
I can't give you a clear answer.
But emotionally,
it might be because Mr. Chan
brought that scrapbook to Ms. Nalin
and talked to her for a good while.
Mr. Chan called me earlier,
and asked me to let you know
if you showed up.
Please excuse me.
Yes. I'm the one
who asked the doctor to tell you.
If even your aunt is fighting,
why won't you?
Auntie.
Jinla wants you to have this scrapbook.
I'll leave it here for you.
HEN AND HER CHICK
YOU AND ME
Your niece must have been
a troublemaker as a kid.
Wow.
Where was this photo taken?
Come to think of it,
you and your niece look a lot alike.
LIFE IS PERFECT
THIS DEGREE IS FOR YOU, AUNT
You knew all along that
my aunt is my weakness.
You knew that if you said that to me,
I would come back to you.
I didn't know if you'd come back.
All I know is
I have to keep my promise to you.
That I'll give your aunt the best care.
Why did you do that to me?
I know you're mad at me
for using you as bait.
But I need you to know I did it for you.
Did you think Ms. Cha would let you live
if she found out
you weren't the real Claire?
What are you doing?
Listening to music.
I can't focus.
Hey, you need to learn to relax.
Seeing you stressed all day
makes me worry you'll get an aneurysm.
If you want me to relax,
just sit there and keep quiet.
I need to ask you something.
But my question...
might be a bit upsetting.
What is it?
The day of the crash.
What about it?
Do you remember seeing the pilot
drink or eat anything that day?
The police called
about the pilot's blood test.
They found GHB in his blood.
No, I... I don't remember.
Hey, I know this is hard,
but try to remember.
I really need to know.
I really don't remember.
I was focused on
what Ms. Claire was saying at the time.
I didn't pay attention to anything else.
Why ask all of a sudden?
It's nothing.
You know I'm a detail-oriented person.
I was just wondering.
By the way, are you hungry?
I haven't eaten all day.
What do you think?
What are you in the mood for, huh?
I thought you'd want
something more special.
I'm addicted to instant food.
Just kidding.
This is very special.
Think about it. Would someone
like Ms. Claire ever eat instant ramen?
No way.
So this is very special.
Hey.
What?
You smiled.
I did what?
You smiled. I saw just now.
- I didn't.
- Did too.
- It's the first time I've seen you smile.
- Did not.
I said I didn't smile.
Just admit it. No need to be shy.
- You're seeing things.
- Seeing things?
You look good when you smile.
Why not smile more?
I said I didn't smile.
In denial.
Don't forget to delete the photos.
Is something wrong?
No, just work stuff.
Excuse me for a second.
I'll be right back.
Ah, that's better.
Do you remember seeing
the pilot drink or eat anything that day?
Sorry. Are you okay?
I spilled your coffee.
It's fine.
Hey.
I remember now, about what you asked.
What is it?
I remember the pilot drank coffee
before boarding.
He drank coffee?
Did you recover
the data from Claire's phone?
Do you know anything
about Ms. Claire and Mr. Chan?
I want to know if they had a fight,
or if there was something more serious.
He wants Ms. Claire dead.
I think we should get rid
of Claire quickly.
If she becomes the chairman,
she won't keep us around.